{
  "query": "top things to do in raining season",
  "engine": "yahoo",
  "title": "top things to do in raining season - Yahoo Search Results",
  "firstHeading": "Rainy Day Activities: 123 Fun Things to Do When it Rains",
  "qa": [
    {
      "question": "Things",
      "answer": "Today, we’ll share some fantastic ideas for things to do when it rains. You can create a warm atmosphere at home, or take a splashy adventure outside. So grab your favorite drink, and let’s turn that rainy day into a memorable one!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Activities",
      "answer": "Outdoor activities on a rainy day – Go for a rain hike, make rain music, splash in puddles, and build a dam. Indoor activities – Have a movie marathon, camp indoors, make a snack, have a treasure hunt, and play board games."
    },
    {
      "question": "Fun things to do",
      "answer": "After a long week of work, sometimes we just want to use our free time to enjoy ourselves. These fun things to do can all be done indoors, and are perfect if you just want to have a good time."
    },
    {
      "question": "To",
      "answer": "Want to use your indoor time to try something different? These creative and unique ideas can help you use your creative energy and discover new things and experiences."
    },
    {
      "question": "To",
      "answer": "If the rain is lashing down and you are confined to your home or apartment, that doesn’t mean a day of staring out the window has to pass you by. There’s still plenty of fun to be had at home, as these things you can do prove."
    },
    {
      "question": "To",
      "answer": "Want to put that indoor time to good use. Get organized, learn a new skill, or exert some creative energy with these productive things to do."
    },
    {
      "question": "Raining",
      "answer": "Just because it’s raining outside, that doesn’t mean you can be with those nearest and dearest to you. Get your squad together in WhatsApp, and pitch them some of these great ideas."
    },
    {
      "question": "To do",
      "answer": "Money a little tight? No problem! There’s still plenty to do when it’s pouring outside that costs very little, if anything. A little resourcefulness and an adventurous spirit are all you need for these rainy-day budget ideas."
    },
    {
      "question": "Things to do",
      "answer": "With a little creativity and imagination, entertaining the kids on a rainy day can be a hugely fun experience for everyone. These things to do should give you some great ideas."
    },
    {
      "question": "38. create your own indoor mini golf at home",
      "answer": "38. Create Your Own Indoor Mini Golf at Home"
    },
    {
      "question": "To",
      "answer": "Order a simple putting machine with a club and ball, and get creative around your home. Use cushions, chairs, toys, and boxes to create a fun mini-golf obstacle course around your home, and see how many strokes it takes to complete."
    },
    {
      "question": "39. make paper airplanes and decorate them",
      "answer": "39. Make Paper Airplanes and Decorate Them"
    },
    {
      "question": "To",
      "answer": "Simple to make, you can use newspaper or colored paper, or pens and paints to design beautiful skins for your airplanes before you fold them."
    },
    {
      "question": "In",
      "answer": "40. Join an Online Dance Party in 90s Attire"
    },
    {
      "question": "Scour your closets for clothes that represent this iconic era for dance music, and let loose on an online dance party. strut your stuff, and dance like no one cares.",
      "answer": "Scour your closets for clothes that represent this iconic era for dance music, and let loose on an online dance party. Strut your stuff, and dance like no one cares."
    }
  ],
  "keywords": [
    "top things to do in raining season"
  ],
  "links": [],
  "debug": {
    "searchUrl": "https://search.yahoo.com/search?p=top%20things%20to%20do%20in%20raining%20season",
    "totalPairs": 15,
    "timestamp": "2025-06-09T17:18:06.061Z"
  }
}